Sedares, Constantine Collection of Federation of Union Representatives (FOUR) Files 6249
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Constantine Sedares Collection of Federation of Union Representatives (FOUR) Files
1953- 1964
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Sedares, Constantine
6249
4 cubic feet
4 linear ft.
Records.
This collection consists of proceedings, press releases, communications, leafltets and clippings of the Federation of Union Representatives (FOUR).
6246225
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, March 20, 2008
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 07, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5780/002: ILGWU David Dubinsky Correspondence 5780/081: ILGWU Legal Department Records 5780/082: ILGWU James Lipsig Papers 5780/088: ILGWU Gus Tyler Papers
Unfair labor practices -- United States; Women's clothing industry -- United States; Clothing workers -- United States; Industrial relations -- United States; Sedares, Constantine.; Federation of Union Representatives; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union
6246225
- Representation Proceedings. (Part 1), 1961 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Representation Proceedings. (Part 2), 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Scope and Contents
  Communications
- NLBB Representation Proceedings. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Includes affidavit
- Notes., 1961 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Review of searches
- Notes., 1962 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Statement at Speech at TI Graduation, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- FOUR Elections., 1963 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Ballots. (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Harrassment., 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Notes.
- Harrassment. Kochian, Ed., 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Harrassment. Crowley, John., 1961 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Unfair Labor Practices. Temple, James., 1961 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Mike Gross Letters, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Shuman Cohen Gross (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Waymon Mitchell Unfair Labor Practices Case., 1961 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Herb Levitt Unfair Labor Practices Case, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Patricia Levenstein Unfair Labor Practices Case, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Statements Unfair Labor Practices Case, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Federation of Unior Representatives: Representation Proceedings., 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Refusal to Bargain., 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Refusal to Bargain, Court Action. (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Wage Increase, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- General Counsel's Exceptions to immediate report (Box 2, Folder 5)
- FOUR Unfair Labor Practices Case (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Court Appeals Action (Box 2, Folder 7)
- FOUR election Petition- NLRP (Box 2, Folder 8)
- 2nd Bloom Case, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Petition for Section 10(j) Injunction., 1962 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Events., 1961 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Distributions at Conventions., 1961 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Press Releases., 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Resignations From FOUR., 1961 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Office of Manpower Programming Ass., Position Holders (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Newsletters. Misc., 1960-1962 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Newsletters., 1963 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Newsletters. (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Newsletters. (Box 3, Folder 9)
- FOUR Newsletters., 1960-1961 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Communications. Personal., 1961-1963 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Communications. ILGWU, 1960-1962 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Communications. Cooper, Mitchell., 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Communications. Thomas, Norman., 1961 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Communications - 1960 (Box 3, Folder 14A)
- Communications. (Part 1), 1961 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Communications. (Part 2), 1961 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Delinbe of the Labor system by Solomon Barkin, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Communications -1962 (Jan-June) (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Communications - 1962 (July-December) (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Communications -1963 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Communications -1964 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Press Releases., 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Press Releases and Publicity., 1961 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Events., 1961 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Leaflets., 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- McMullen Misc., 1960 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- ILGWU. Training Institute., 1960 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Federal Telephone and Radio Co., 1953-1957 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Tiny Town Togs., 1960 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Little Tots Dress Company., 1960 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- ILGWU Notes., 1960 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- ILGWU. Convention., 1962 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Election Propaganda (Box 4, Folder 11)
- McMullen- Retail Accounts / Working lists by area (Box 4, Folder 12)
- McMullen- Retail Accounts- NYC (Box 4, Folder 13)
- McMullen- visits to NYC (Box 4, Folder 14)
- McMullen- Retail Accounts- anywhere but NYC (Box 4, Folder 15)
- McMullen- Misc. Letters to Affiliates- (part 1 of 3) (Box 4, Folder 16)
- McMullen- Misc. Letters to Affiliates (Part 2 of 3) (Box 4, Folder 17)
- McMullen- Misc. Letters to Affiliates (Part 3 of 3) (Box 4, Folder 18)
- McMullen- Retail Campaign (Box 4, Folder 19)
  Leaflets, etc.
- McMullen- Leaflets (Box 4, Folder 20)
- McMullen- letters (Box 4, Folder 21)
- McMullen- Eastown region, NYC, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  Sat. Sept 17
- McMullen- memos re: retail campaigns, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- McMullen-Letters to retail accounts, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  May-August
- Misc. Leaflets, letters (Box 4, Folder 25)
- National Labor Relations Board Portfolio (Box 4, Folder 26)